Arista Tiara Madasari

Jakarta, Indonesia



aristatmada@gmail.com



+62 81271446644

Summary

Project Manager with 7+ years of extensive experience in the IT Industry and 3+ years of experience in simultanously managing banking application development and implementation project.

Excel at liasing between business and technical areas to achieve project completion. Able to merge user needs with business requirements, budgetary restrictions and logistical considerations to meet project deliverables.

Key Skills:

- Project Lifecycle Management
- Enterprise Implementation
- System Migration
- Requirement Definition and Analysis
- Project Scheduling
- Team Building and Leadership
- Project Budgeting & Cost Control
- Quality Assurance

Experience



mander IT Project Manager

PT Bank Mandiri (Persero) Tbk. Jul 2017 - Present (3 years 4 months +)

IT Project Manager

Niaga Prima Paramitra Apr 2015 - Jul 2017 (2 years 4 months) Project Manager for Mobile Apps Development



Project Manager

PT. Global Innovation Technology

May 2013 - Apr 2015 (2 years)

Project Manager for ICT Security and SOA Solution Specialist



Project Admin

PT. Global Innovation Technology Nov 2012 - Jun 2013 (8 months)



Teller (Operational Staff)

PT. Bank Bukopin Tbk 2011 - 2012 (2 years)

Education



Institut Teknologi Bandung

Master of Business Administration (M.B.A.), Business Leadership Executive 2014 - 2016

Universitas Lampung (Unila)

Bachelor of Computer Science, Computer Science 2006 - 2010

STIE Gentiaras

Bachelor's Degree, Economics 2006 - 2010

Additional Training:

2013 - 2018

- 1. Porject Management Body Of Knowledge (PMBOK) Training
- 2. User Experience (UX) Training
- 3. BSMR Level 2
- 4. PRINCE 2

Licenses & Certifications



PRINCE2® Foundation Certification Training

Skills

Project Management • Business Analysis • PMP • Requirements Analysis • Software Documentation • Software Project Management • Software Quality Assurance • IT Project Lifecycle • Budgeting • Software Implementation

Projects

Business Process Reengineering – Loan Origination System (LOS) Small Medium Enterprise at PT Bank
Mandiri

Jul 2019 – Present

Business Process Reengineering – Loan Origination System (LOS) Kredit Serbaguna Mandiri at PT Bank
Mandiri

Jul 2017 - Jul 2019

Business Process Reengineering – Loan Origination System (LOS) Kredit Pemilikan Rumah at PT Bank
Mandiri

Jul 2017 - Jul 2019

XTimo Mobile Application for Bina Artha at PT Bina Artha Ventura

Sep 2016 - Jun 2017

ACC Mobile Application at PT Astra Credit Company

Sep 2015 - Jun 2017

Enhancement ORACLE Identity Manager (IDM) Phase 4 for SPAM System at BTPN

Dec 2014 - Mei 2015

Implementation IBM Security Identity Manager (ISIM) at JASINDO

Dec 2014 - Sep 2015

• Green Plum Datamart - Data Warehouse at PT XL Axiata

Feb 2016 - Feb 2016

XL Tunai MGM Mobile Application at PT XL Axiata

Apr 2015 - Apr 2015

Implementation ORACLE Identity Manager (IDM) to Zimbra Mail Server at BTPN

Nov 2014 - Nov 2014

• Handheld Collection System (Micro Mobile System) - Mandiri Mikro

Oct 2014 - Oct 2014

 Mobile Application System Delivery Service Support, Sales Executive Dan Unit Referral - MANDIRI Credit Cards Group

Oct 2014 - Oct 2014

• Implementasi ORACLE Identity Management System Phase 3 - BTPN

Aug 2014 - Aug 2014

PT Asuransi JASINDO (ESSO-IBM Implementation)

Mar 2014

• Bank BTPN (Account Statement)

Dec 2013

• PT. NTT Data Indonesia Web Portal

Oct 2013

Bank Mandiri Micro Mobile System (MMS)

Jul 2013

• Bank BTPN Configuring WebSphere 7.0

May 2013

• XL Company Identity Manager (IdM)

Feb 2013